[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stallone studied drama at this University, but dropped out and returned to New York, where he made appearances in a few small off-Broadway plays.", "correct_answer": "The University of Miami", "incorrect_answers": ["The University of Charleston", "The University of Alabama", "The University of the Arts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Dan Aykroyd of Saturday Night Live fame has a cameo in the movie Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does John Dillingers girlfriend do when she is beaten during the interrogation following her arrest in the 2009 Public Enemies movie?", "correct_answer": "She does not betray John.", "incorrect_answers": ["She seduces the interrogator and manages to escape.", "She kills the interrogator.", "She decides to speak and discloses Johns location."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of the popular spice saffron, which has an Arabic origin?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Poison", "Aroma", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the first movie produced outside the USA or England to win the Academy Award for Best Picture?", "correct_answer": "The Last Emperor", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bridge Over the River Kwai", "Gladiator", "Out of Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Central Processing Unit (aka CPU) responsible for?", "correct_answer": "Executing computer programs", "incorrect_answers": ["Advising US governments on internal matters", "Turning crude oil into gasoline", "Crime Prevention"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the Pascaline invented?", "correct_answer": "1645", "incorrect_answers": ["1601", "1636", "1886"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Generally milk stays fresh for up to a week after the sell by or pull date.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chameleons are lizards that can change their colour. What does Chameleon mean in Greek?", "correct_answer": "Earth lion", "incorrect_answers": ["Green melon", "Karma lion", "Colourful"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the lights in our homes wired in?", "correct_answer": "parallel", "incorrect_answers": ["circuits", "pairs", "series"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rick Moranis and Steve Martin or Jack Nicholson and Jonathan Haze in a flower store.", "correct_answer": "Little Shop of Horrors", "incorrect_answers": ["On A Clear Day, You Can See Forever", "Flowers for Algernon", "Night of the Living Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the methods used by viruses to make the host cell release the newly produced viruses?", "correct_answer": "Virosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Apoptosis", "Budding", "Lysis"]}]